newbizshop.com 2013-05-30

# Privacy - NewBiz Advertising Blog

Your **privacy** is of utmost importance to us here at NewBiz Advertising Blog. Rest assured that any information you provide will only be used in accordance with this **privacy** statement.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Newbiz Advertising Blog collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http:// **newbizshop.com**](http://newbizshop.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Newbiz Advertising Blog.

## Personal identification information

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-Personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web Browser Cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## How We Use Collected Information

Newbiz Advertising Blog collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes.

**_To improve customer service_** :

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

**_To send periodic emails_** :

The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.

## How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## Third Party Websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensers and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own **privacy** policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This **privacy** policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network **privacy** policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

## Compliance With Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

Protecting the **privacy** of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

Newbiz Advertising Blog has the discretion to update this **privacy** policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this **privacy** policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this **Privacy** Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
admin@newbizshop.com

This document was last updated on Feb. 3rd, 2013

  * Bio
  * Twitter
  * Facebook
  * Google+
  * LinkedIn
  * Latest Posts

Derek is a super moderator on the v7n Network community. He spends most of his time helping people out on the forum and drinks a lot of coffee. Derek has been in the affiliate marketing niche for a long time and blogs part-time which is really like a full time job. What is this thing called sleep?

#### [@snakeair2](http://twitter.com/snakeair2)

I run a free advertising blog and been in affiliate marketing for a long time. Follow me for valuable content from my blog and other content i tweet from V7N.

Facebook Starts Verifying Popular Pages & Profiles <http://t.co/En5GhbsdG0> via [@marketingland](http://twitter.com/marketingland "Follow marketingland") \- 40 mins ago
